Guide to the Walter Wilson Greg Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Prints of Title Pages and Portraits, circa 1800-1959, undated; Series VII; 0.21; (1 box)
  - Contains Prints of Title Pages, Portraits of English Poets Playwrights (Some Used in Bibliography of English Printed Drama ) (Box 5)
- Manuscripts of Greg's Articles and Lectures, Lists, circa 1925-1959, undated; Series VIII; 0.42; (1 box)
  Lists and manuscripts of articles and lectures by Greg, particularly on the textual criticism of Shakespeare.
  - Listings of Shakespeare Quartos: Locations, Conditions, Dates of Publication: Notebook and Loose Sheets. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - MSS of Articles and Lectures (incl. "Reference by Signatures," "Oliver Cromwell As An Actor," A Preface, "The Elements of Textual Criticism in Shakespeare's Plays," "The Comparative Bibliography of Manuscripts and Printed Books, and the Significance of Filial Texts," "Transcript and Quotation," "For Queen and Country," "The Text of King Lear," "What is Bibliography?" [Typed Script]). (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - A "Book of Links" in MS. Details Contracts and Links Between Stationers in the Production of Plays. Bound Sheets. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 2 Transcriptions of Jonson's Masque of Gipsies, Each Bound (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
- Personal Family Items, Photographs, 1900-1950, undated; Series IX; 0.21; (1 box)
  Personal items including a school report, a few photographs of Greg, and a printed universal calendar calculator.
  - Miscellaneous personal materials., 1900-1950 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous Manuscript Fragments and Documents, 1559-1707; Series X; 0.42; (1 box); Material is filed in two groups: original manuscript material is followed by photostats and photocopies of documents.
  Series X contains original early modern documents as well as photocopies and photostats of them, all collected by Greg in the course of his research. Original documents include a legal document on parchment signed by the poet Sir John Suckling; a royal household letter from 1622 signed by Oliver Cromwell and Henry Vane the elder, among others; and a Sir Francis Fane letter with his seal.
  - Miscellaneous MS Fragments in Latin, Italian, Dutch. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Paper Specimens. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bond, Dennis, d. 1658 LS to Sir George Asrud (?) Whitehall 1 p. 24 x 35 cm. Concerns Converting Dutch Vessel into Man-of-War, 1652 July 16 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Suckling, Sir John, 1569-1627 LS TO ? 1 p. 27 x 8 cm. In Latin; Reference to Victualling Without License, 1617 June 23 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hull, J ALS T. Thomas Law London 1 p. 31 x 19 cm. Legal Agreement for Purchase of real estate on verso; signed by Ri[chard?] Webb., 1707 January 19 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Foster, William ALS to Mr. Hull Wappenham 3 p. 20 x 31 cm. Concerns Foster's Last Will and Testament, included on verso p. 1., 1707 December 29 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 1600-1649, Household LS to George Norton London 1 p. 23 x 33 cm. Instructions to cut and sell 400 timber trees at Henton Manor; Signed by Sir Oliver Cromwell, Henry Vane The Elder, Lord Andover et. al., 1622 February 19 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Carey, Robert, First Earl of Monmouth, 1560(?)-1639 1 p. 20 x 30 cm. Announcement, signed by Carey and Sir Peter Young, of John Drew's Petition for Funds., 1619 September (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 1566-1625 Westminster 2 p. 24 x 36 cm. Letter of Privy Seal, to receive from Oliver Style the sum of £500. Signed by Lord Thomas Kerry and Francis Godolphin., 1603 February 28 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Curtis, John 1 p. 20 x 31 cm. Petition for land granted to Allen Foster. Signed and witnessed., 1645 September 20 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Goodday, William London 1 p., with seal, 20 x 31 cm. Petition concerning sale of mare., 1672 October 21 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Humphrey, Christopher 1 p. 20 x 31 cm. Petition stating relationship to Edward Hellier. Signed and witnessed., 1652 May 10 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lovermore, Richard et al. Honyton 1 p. 21 x 40 cm. Judgment against Thomas Humphrey Signed by Ambrose Cleake, John Avery, Rober Lowe, John Smythe, George Clark, Humphrey Long., 1662 April 13 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Nell, Christopher 1 p. 21 x 32 cm. Bill, signed with X, for payment of 50 s. to Vincent Amcokes(?), fishmonger., 1559 October 23 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Fane, Sir Francis, d. 1689? 1 p. 21 x 40 cm. Document selling Grinnelse Wateringbury to John Wright. With Seal of Sir Francis Fane; on vellum; in Latin; signed by Thomas Ratchfield, William Lorkyn, ?, Horman., 1615 October 30 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ? 1 p. 22 x 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - ? Padua 1 p. 22 x 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - ? 1 p. 22 x 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Satoke, John(?) 1 p. 16 x 27 cm. An opinion on legal question of land sale., 1655 July 11 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Misc. photographs/photostats of deeds, indentures, lists. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Autograph, William Shakespeare.
    - Autographs, various members of city companies [Bod. MS].
    - Autograph, Simon Forman (d. 1611) on Lambeth deed of 1606.
    - Face of the Symonds deed, autograph John Bingham.
    - Deed, autographed by William Symonds.
    - Deed between Sir John Bourchies and Christopher Brooke.
    - Deed relating to the "Three Tuns" Tavern [cf. Robt. Herrick].
    - Deed, autographed by William Strachey
    - Deed, witnessed by Phillip Henslowe
    - Deed, relating to Magdelene College, Oxford; witnessed by Phillip Henslowe
    - In original envelopes used by WWG Sale catalogue (1687) of Burghley's MSS and Corpus Cristi College MS 114 pp. 447,491,492,497,503,779, 831,849,897.
    - List of Prince Henry's Players [B.M. MS Hartley 252 fols. 5,10] Also printed in Gentleman's Magazine v. CCC n. 67 February 1906 [cf. Box]; Fairfax's Eighth Eclogue [B.M. MS Add 11743 fols. 5-6] Also printed in MLQ v. IV n. 85 July 1901.
    - Oswald: A dramatic fragment [B.M. MS Egerton 2623 fols. 37-38] Also printed in MLQ v. VII n. 148 December 1904; Bishop
    - Grindal ALS to Burghley 22 February 1563/4, concerning plays in times of infection. Also printed in Malone Society's Collections v. 1 n. 14 June 1909.
    - Theatrical repertories in 1662 [B.M. MS Sloane 1900 fols. 65-60. Also printed in The Gentleman's Magazine v. CCCI n. 69 July 1906. [cf. Box 3].
    - Richard Robinson's Eupolemia [B.M. MS Royal 18A LXVI fols. 5-13]
    - Richard Robinson, Citizen of London (1648) Title Page [Yale].
    - The Proclamation of 16 November 1538 and related documents: MS Cotton E. v. fols. 364-67
    - Sir Thomas Elyot Dictionary 1538 [sic 7659: B.M. C. 28 M. 2 A1v]
    - Epistles and Gospels 1540 [sic 2967: B.M. C.25 q.9]
    - The Door of Holy Scripture (Wycliffe's translation of the Bible) 1540 [sic 3033: B.M. C.25 d. 7/1 Alv]
    - Richard Srafton ALS to Thomas Cromwell 1 Dec 1538 [B.B. MS Cotton Cleop. E. v. fol. 346].
    - Townely and Chester Plays [Hunt. HM 1 fol. 62-64].
  - Facimilies of Shakespeare documents and signatures. (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Correspondence, 1905-1959; Series XI; 0.42; (1 box)
  Alphabetically arranged by correspondent.
  Series XI contains scholarly and professional letters received by Greg, mostly on Shakespeare and on the Bibilography of the English Printed Drama. Major correspondents include E. K. Chambers, D. M. Davin, A.W. Pollard, Evelyn Simpson, and Kenneth Sisam.
  There are detailed subject notes on many of the letters in the list below.
  - Adams, Joseph Quincy, 1881-1946 ALS to WW Greg 1935 October 16, Washington - remarks on Greg's edition of Antichrist and comments on galley proofs for BED. 1941 August 22, Washington - remarks on R.B. McKerrow LS to WW Greg 1945 May 9, Washington - comments on death of Roosevelt 1945 May 12, Washington - on Davenant's Seige of Rhodes (Frag) (Box 9)
  - Adams, Thomas R. LS to WW Greg 1951 November 15, Philadelphia - Textual issues in Jonson's Works and Thomas Killegrew's Comedies and Tragedies. (Box 9)
  - Alexander, Peter, 1893- ALS to WW Gregg 1933 August 3, Cornwall - on punctuation of King Lear 1951 May 28, Glasgow - Shakespearean textual issues. 1955 December 8, Glasgow - remarks on Aristotle's theory of catharsis. (Box 9)
  - Atkinson, R. d.E LS to WW Greg 1946 June 14, Greenwich - explanation of planetary periods. (Box 9)
  - Bald, Robert Cecil, 1901- ALS to WW Greg 1933 February 22, Ithaca, NY 1945 September 23, Ithaca, NY (Box 9)
  - Bastin, Frank E. ALS to WW Greg 1922 October 15, London - on primacy of Shirley texts. (Box 9)
  - Batey, Charles LS to WW Greg 1955 March 30, Oxford-(enclosure wanting) 1955 March 31, Oxford - concerns missing negatives. (Box 9)
  - Beattie, William ALS to WW Greg 1947 October 12, Edinburgh - corrections to BED. (Box 9)
  - Bentley, Gerald Eades, 1901- ALS to WW Greg 1925 December 18, London LS to WW Greg 1954 February 12, Princeton - concerns Elizabethan stage and laws. (Box 9)
  - Blagden, Cyprian LS to WW Greg 1955 November 10, London (Box 9)
  - Bliss, Leslie E. LS to WW Greg 1955 April 7, San Marino - reproduction permission. (Box 9)
  - Boas, Frederick Samuel, 1862-1957 ALS to WW Greg 1950 May 18, Wimbledon - editions, editorial issues in Doctor Faustus. (Box 9)
  - Bone, Gavin David, 1907-1942 ALS to WW Greg 1937 April 20, Oxford - editorial issues in The Assembly of the Gods and The Seige of Thebes. (Box 9)
  - Bowers, Fredson Thayer, 1905- AL to WW Greg 1958 September 14, University, Virginia - textual issues in Sandy's Christ's Passion ALS to WW Greg 1950 February 16 (Box 9)
  - Boyd, Julian Parks, 1903- LS to WW Greg 1947 January 2, Princeton (Box 9)
  - Bradley, Andrew Cecil, 1851-1935. ALS to WW Greg 1909 March 31, Kensington (Box 9)
  - Bradley, Henry, 1845-1923 ALS to WW Greg 1912 January 27, Oxford - textual comments on Assumption Play. 1914 May 21, Oxford 1916 March 8, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Bullen, Arthur Henry, 1857-1920 ALS to WW Greg 1905 August 19, Stratford-on-Avon (Box 9)
  - Byrne, Muriel St. Claire, 1895- ALS to WW Greg 1950 May 14, St. John's Wood Terrace 1950 May 19, St. John's Wood Terrace - congratulations on knighthood. (Box 9)
  - Chambers, Sir Edmund Kerchever, 1866-1954 ALS to WW Greg 1930 Nov 16, Bynsham, Oxford - travels in Canada and USA (enclosed photo wanting) 1931 January 18, Eynsham (2 p.) 1931 November 10, Eynsham 1936 June 26, Eynsham 1938 November 21, Oxford - concerns Chamber's opinion of an Elizabethan performance of Hamlet 1940 February 27, Devon 1940 July 26, Devon (2 p.) remarks on Chester Cycle Plays 1941 April 1, Devon 1941 September 29, Devon (Box 9)
  - Chapman, Robert William, 1881-1960 ALS to WW Greg 1945 September 21, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Charnlern, Clara L. LS to WW Greg 1936 May 9, - Concerns a volume of Holinshed's Chronicles, suggested perhaps to be a personal copy of Shakespeare (enclosure wanting) (Box 9)
  - Clements, T.Y.B. ALS to WW Greg 1936 January 29 - Concerns Burghley catalog (enclosure wanting) (Box 9)
  - Crawford, Charles ALS to WW Greg 1931 July 4, London (Box 9)
  - Crow, John ALS to WW Greg 1950 March 11, London (enclosure wanting) 1956 July 4, Washington - concerns textual variants in Richard III 1956 Jul 4, Washington undated, Cambridge (Box 9)
  - Davin, Daniel Marcus, 1913- LS to WW Greg [unless otherwise noted Davin's correspondences concern the production and publication of the Oxford Press Shakespeare Series] 1954 May 20, Oxford 1954 May 20, Oxford 1955 Jun 21, Oxford 1955 August 22, Oxford 1955 October 18, Oxford 1956 January 25, Oxford (dictated but not signed) 1956 June 5, Oxford 1956 June 8, Oxford 1956 August 20, Oxford 1956 August 29, Oxford 1957 Jan 1, Oxford 1957 May 22, Oxford 1957 May 27, Oxford 1957 August 16, Oxford 1958 April 8, Oxford 1958 April 16, Oxford 1959 February 7, Oxford - concern publication of Greg's collected works. (Box 9)
  - Downs, Robert Bingham, 1903- LS to WW Greg 1949 May 26, Urbana - concerns Tatham's The Scots Figgaries 1949 June 23, Urbana (with enclosure) (Box 9)
  - Duthie, George Ian LS to WW Greg 1949 February 26, Montreal 1950 June 4, Montreal (Box 9)
  - Edwards, C.K. LS to WW Greg 1927 February 3, San Marino - concerns Huntington copy of Rosamond and Cleopatra (with enclosed letter from Rosenbach Company) 1933 December 28, San Marion - regarding variant copies of Gascoigne's Works. (Box 9)
  - Ferguson, Frederick Sutherland, 1878-1967 ALS to WW Greg 1921 September 6, Wimbledon - description of Gascoigne's Works (1587) 1925 June 12, Palmer's Green - description of Cartwright's Comedies, Tragedies and Other Works (1651) 1925 June 26, - note on Cartwright volume sold at auction. 1925 September 14, London - textual remarks on Cartwright (enclosure wanting) 1926 August 19, Palmer's Green 1934 April 13, Southgate - notes on Chapman's May-Day (1611) 1934 April 16, Palmer's Green 1938 August 4, Palmer's Green AL to WW Greg 1942 September 12, Palmer's Green AL Frag. to WW Greg? (Box 9)
  - Fleur, F.G. ALS to WW Greg 1907 March(?) 6, Upper Tooting 1907 March 25, Upper Tooting (Box 9)
  - Francis, Sir Frank Charlton, 1901- LS to WW Greg 1948 May 20, London 1949 September 29, London - remarks on The Scots Figgaries (Box 9)
  - Fripp, Edgar Innes, d. 1931 ALS to WW Greg 1931, July 20 - criticism to Chamber's William Shakespeare (Box 9)
  - Fry, Mary Isabel LS to WW Greg 1956 July 26, San Marino - description of Huntington Mid-Night Dream 1956 Aug 17, San Marino - description of Huntington Henry IV Part I (Box 9)
  - Gibson, L. ALS to WW Greg 1929 April 30, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Goff, Frederick Richmond, 1916- LS to WW Greg 1948 February 27, Washington, D.C. - description of T. Rawlins' The Rebellion (Box 9)
  - Gollacz(?), Isaac ALS to WW Greg 1917 November 7, Melrose (Box 9)
  - Grace, Charles L. LS to WW Greg 1956 August 7, Cambridge, Mass. - concerns Aarvard's A Midsommer Night's Dreme (1600) (Box 9)
  - Grant, Isabelle F. LS to WW Greg 1949 July 8, Urbana - Ke: Tatham's Scots Figgaries (cf. LS from R.B. Downs) 1949 August 3, Urbana - Re: Tatham's Scots Figgaries (Box 9)
  - Hanson, G.B. ALS to WW Greg 1935 December 6, London - concerns Shakespeare holographs, esp. with Holinshed Volume (Box 9)
  - Haraszti, Zoltan, 1892- LS to WW Greg 1940 February 14, Boston - textual notes on Thomas Randolph's Aristoppus (1630) 1956 June 28, Boston - description of A Midsommer Night's Dreme (1600) (Box 9)
  - Hill, R.H. ALS to WW Greg 1922 October 23, Oxford - description of James Shirley's Honoria and Mammon (photostats enclosed) (Box 9)
  - Hinman, Charlton LS to WW Greg 1940 May 10, Charlottsville, VA - queries on printing and proofreading techniques, esp. in relation to Greg's study of the printing of King Lear (Box 9)
  - Howarth, Robert Guy, 1908- ALS to WW Greg 1930 November 17, Oxford - concerns editing papers of Lord Henry Herbert 1931 May 2, Oxford- (Box 9)
  - Hulls, Leonard G. LS to WW Greg 1944 October 17, Sussex (enclosures wanting) (Box 9)
  - Hulme, Hilda M. ALS to WW Greg 1956 February 22, London (enclosure wanting) (Box 9)
  - Jackson, William Alexander, 1905-1964 LS to WW Greg 1927 October 29, Williamstown, Mass. re: Henry Glapthorne's Wit in A Constable (1640) 1933 November 22, London - description of Gascoigne's Works (1587) 1944 July 12, Cambridge, Mass. (Box 9)
  - Johnson, John De Monins, 1882-1956 LS to WW Greg 1930 October 11, Oxford 1945 August 2, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Jones, W.B. ALS to WW Greg 1932 February 11, Eton 1932 February 26, Eton 1932 July 14, Eton (Box 9)
  - Kadison, Alexander LS to WW Greg 1955 November 12, New York (Box 9)
  - Keen, G. Alan ALS to WW Greg 1936 August 11, Edgware (photostat of possible autograph of Shakespeare enclosed) 1936 August 14, Edgware 1936 August 23, Edgware 1936 August 25, Edgware (Box 9)
  - Ker, Neil Ripley LS to WW Greg 1944 May 25, Oxford (photographs enclosed wanting) (Box 9)
  - Ker, William Paton, 1855-1925 ALS to WW Greg 1917 December 10 1918 February 1, London (Box 9)
  - Kirschbaum, Leo, 1907- LS to WW Greg 1951 May 21, Detroit 1951 December 2 (Box 9)
  - Kocher, Paul Harold, 1907- LS to WW Greg 1948 November 29, Claremont, Calif. - queries on publication date of Dr. Faustus (Box 9)
  - Lawler, Percy E. LS to WW Greg 1939 July 18, Philadelphia (photostats of Middleton's Triumphs of Honor and Virtue (1622) enclosed) (Box 9)
  - Leconfield, Hugh Archibald Wyndham, Baron, 1877- LS to WW Greg 1946 February 2, Detworth (Box 9)
  - Lee, Sir Sidney, 1859-1929 ALS to WW Greg 1905 December 27, Kensington - necrological information on Elizabeth, Countess of Rutland 1905 December 28, Kensington 1905 December 30, Kensington (Box 9)
  - Lerch, Alice H. LS to WW Creg 1940 June 14, Washington, D.C. - comparison of Houghton and Library of Congress Volumes of John Ford's The Broken Heart (1633). (Box 9)
  - MacDonald, Hugh, 1885- ALS to WW Greg 1945 April 7, Cambridge undated, - concerns Greg's tribute to R.B. McKerrow (Box 9)
  - MacKail, John William, 1859-1945 ALS to WW Greg 1928 May 24, Kensington (Box 9)
  - McKerrow, Amy ALS to WW Greg 1941 August 3, Cambridge - thanks for Greg's tribute to R. B. McKerrow (Box 9)
  - McKerrow, Ronald Brunlees, 1872-1940 ALS to WW Greg 1907 March 27, Manchester Square - comments on Boswell MS 3129 and licensing of plays 1924 April 11, London - theory of B.M. copy of (?) 1939 August 9, Wendover - retraction of his theory of Elizabethan printing and proofing techniques (Box 9)
  - McManaway, James Gilmer, 1899- ALS to WW Greg 1945 September 20, Washington (2 pp.) LS to WW Greg 1946 November 13, Washington - announcing death of J.Q. Adams (enclosures wanting) ALS to WW Greg 1950 May 26, Washington - textual points in Dr. Faustus 1952 February 18, Washington - comments on colophons in second folio (Box 9)
  - Mass, G. ALS to WW Greg 1941 January 18, Oxford - comments on Greg's Text of King Lear (Box 9)
  - Macawlay, George Campbell, 1852-1915 ALS to WW Greg 1915 January 22, Cambridge (1915?) January 29, Cambridge (Box 9)
  - Maxwell, J.C. ALS to WW Greg 1948 August 9, Oxford - refutation of P.H. Kocher's claim for Nashe Authorship 1948 August 15, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Mead, Herman Ralph, 1873- LS to WW Greg 1948 June 4, San Marino - notes on Middleton's The Mayor of Quinborough (1661) 1948 July 12, San Marino - notes on Middleton's The Mayor of Quinborough (1661) 1948 July 21, San Marino - textual note on Newes Out of the West (1641) undated - textual notes on Davenant's Siege of Rhodes (1663) (Box 9)
  - Meikle, Henry R. ALS to WW Greg 1947 September 23, Edinborough (Box 9)
  - Moore-Smith, G.C. ALS to WW Greg 1914 September 27, Sheffield - response to Add. MS 29496 1934 April 30, Sheffield 1935 September 18, Sheffield (Box 9)
  - Murphy, Mallie J. LS to WW Greg 1946 November 13, Washington, D.C. - remarks following death of J.Q. Adams (obituary enclosed) (Box 9)
  - Nash, Ray, 1905- LS to WW Greg 1944 June 19, Hanover - comments on "Good Order" (1533) 1944 August 27, Hanover - comments on "Good Order" (1533) 1944 November 3, Hanover ALS to WW Greg 1954 December 27, Hanover (Box 9)
  - Needham, Francis ALS to WW Greg 1926 June 22, Workshop Nolls (Box 9)
  - Pafford, J.W. ALS to WW Greg 1950 February 3, London (Box 9)
  - Partridge, Astley Cooper ALS to WW Greg 1953 August 16, Stratford-on-Avon - spelling in Shakespeare editions (Box 9)
  - Pollard, Alfred William, 1859-1944 ALS to WW Greg 1913 December 21, Alassio 1916 September 11, Wimbledon - feelings on admission of H.C. Folger to Malone Soc. 1916 November 12, London - comments on J.P. Gibson 1916 November 26, Wimbledon - comments on Shakespeare's hand 1916 December 6, Wimbledon 1924 December 16, Wimbledon - comments on current performance of Hamlet 1926 Aug 13, Wimbledon 1933 July 31, Wimbledon (Box 9)
  - Pennington, Richard LS to WW Greg 1951 November 8, Montreal - textual remarks on Jonson's Works (1640 & 41) and Thomas Killigrew's Comedies and Tragedies (1664) (Box 9)
  - Pforzheimer, Carl Howard, 1879-1957 LS to WW Greg 1931 December 16, New York 1947 June 16, Purchase, New York (Box 9)
  - Reed, Alexander Wyclif ALS to WW Greg 1954 February 14, Backwall 1954 February 18, Backwall (Box 9)
  - Renwick, William Lindsay, 1889- ALS to WW Greg 1955 October 29, Edinburgh - comments on Greg's First Folio study (Box 9)
  - Roberts, Colin Henderson, 1909- LS to WW Greg 1956 September 4, Oxford 1956 September 8, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Roberts, Sir Sydney Castle, 1887-1966 LS to WW Greg 1942 August 12, Cambridge 1942 August 28, Cambridge (Box 9)
  - Rosenfeld, Sybil Marion, 1903 ALS to WW Greg 1952 December 5, Bayswater (Box 9)
  - Rutland [William Rutland?l LS to W Greg 1938 March 31, Grantham - concerns Henslowe fragment 1938 May 28, Grantham - concerns Henslowe fragment 1938 December 5, Grantham - concerns Henslowe fragment (Box 9)
  - Scholderer, Victor, 1880- ALS to WW Greg 1938 January 27, London 1955 March 16, London - translation of Heyward's dedication enclosed, transcription by WW Greg laid in 1955 April 6, London - comments on Heyward's dedication (Box 9)
  - Scholfield, A. ALS to WW Greg 1942 September 14, Cambridge (Box 9)
  - Schucking, Levin L. ALS to WW Greg 1952 September 2, Farchant bei Garmisch (Box 9)
  - Simpson, Mrs. Evelyn Mary (Spearing) 1885- ALS to WW Greg _1934 October 25, Oxford - variants in Jonson's Plays (1631) _1937 May 25, Oxford - announcing Percy's intent to take D. Litt. (_Gift of Theodore Besterman) 1942 August 15, Oxford - response to Greg's reviews of Jonson editions (3 p.) 1942 August 30, Oxford undated Oxford - remarks on text of Ben Jonson Works V. IV (3 p.) (Box 9)
  - Sisam, Kenneth LS to WW Greg - concerns Anglo-Saxon phonetics (2 p.) 1925 January 23, Oxford ALS to WW Greg - concerns Anglo-Saxon phonetics (2 p.) 1925 January 27, Oxford LS to WW Greg 1925 January 29, Oxford - concerns Anglo-Saxon phonetics (2 p.) 1926 January 16, Oxford 1932 January 10, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Sisson, Charles Jasper, 1885- ALS to WW Greg 1941 July 30, Littlehampter - remarks on R.W. McKerrow 1943 April 5, Littlehampter (Box 9)
  - Smith, David Nichol, 1875-1962 ALS to WW Greg 1941 August 15, Oxford (Box 9)
  - Spencer, Terence John Bew, 1915- LS to WW Greg 1952 September 27, London - concerns Shakespeare Assn. Quartos series 1952 October 30, London - (LS from Sidgwick & Jackson, LTD enclosed) 1955 December 21, Belfast - concerns Shakespeare Assn. Quartos series. (Box 9)
  - Stevenson, Allan Henry, 1903- LS to WW Greg 1954 August 1, San Marino - concerns Shirley observations (enclosure wanting) (Box 9)
  - Sykes, Henry Dugdale ALS to WW Greg 1925 March 3, Enfield - concerns Thorny Abbey (2 p.) (Box 9)
  - Thompson, E.M. ALS to WW Greg 1916 December 11, Mayfield 1918 April 21, Wimbledon Common - (enclosure wanting) comments on Shakespeare's handwriting, esp. with More frag. (Box 9)
  - Troxell, Gilbert McCoy, 1893-1967 ALS to WW Greg 1940 June 10, New Haven 1947 August 2, New Haven (Box 9)
  - Unger, Emma Virginia LS to WW Greg 1940 December 12, Purchase, New York - with textual notes from Pforzheimer collection (2 p.) (Box 9)
  - Van Lennep, William LS to WW Greg 1948 February 4, Cambridge, Mass. - concerns restoration performance of Monsieur Thomas (Box 9)
  - Walker, Alice LS to WW Greg 1941 August 22, Southport 1957 August 23, Bude, Cornwall (2 p.) (Box 9)
  - Walker, Sir Emery, 1851-1933 LS to WW Greg 1926 November 29, London 1926 December 3, London (2 p.) 1926 December 9, London 1928 February 24, London 1928 February 27, London 1928 Oct 12, London 1928 October 19, London 1929 March 16, London (bill for photographing & engraving charges) 1929 January 31, London (Box 9)
  - Walter, J.H. ALS to WW Greg 1940 April 11, Hadley Wood, Barnet (with enclosure) comments on songs in Glapthorne's Wit in a Constable (Box 9)
  - Wilkinson, Cyril Hackett, 1888-1960 ALS to WW Greg 1942 April 2, Oxford - comments on recent acquisitions (Box 9)
  - Wright, W.J. ALS to WW Greg 1955 January 29, London (enclosures wanting) 1955 July 25, London (tracing of Henslowe's diary fol. 30 enclosed) (Box 9)
- Working Papers, BEPD, Volumes I-II, 1939-1954; Series XII; 0.83; (2 boxes)